[	
{
		"question": "Unscramble the following: ogthrasw",
		"answers": ["Hogwarts"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Unscramble the following: tsduy",
		"answers": ["Study"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Unscramble the following: ecuadtnio",
		"answers": ["Education"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Unscramble the following: prepul",
		"answers": ["Purple"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Unscramble the following: sulh",
		"answers": ["Lush"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Unscramble the following: sretae",
		"answers": ["Easter"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Unscramble the following: ngsehli",
		"answers": ["English"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Unscramble the following: glgauean",
		"answers": ["Language"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Unscramble the following: snecscie",
		"answers": ["Science"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Unscramble the following: iogbylo",
		"answers": ["Biology"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Unscramble the following: isrhyto",
		"answers": ["History"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Unscramble the following: swnreeya",
		"answers": ["New Years"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Unscramble the following: altr ocb",
		"answers": ["Carl Bot"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Unscramble the following: roer eud ttcnhsy",
		"answers": ["The Study Corner"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Unscramble the following: chmerysit",
		"answers": ["Chemistry"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Unscramble the following: olceotyhgn",
		"answers": ["Technology"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Unscramble the following: oercobt",
		"answers": ["October"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Unscramble the following: lcideut osisas",
		"answers": ["Social Studies"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Unscramble the following: lryarib",
		"answers": ["Library"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Unscramble the following: nbit etrsoroo",
		"answers": ["Nitro Booster"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Unscramble the following: studetn",
		"answers": ["Student"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Unscramble the following: gloelce",
		"answers": ["College"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Unscramble the following: edeemrbc",
		"answers": ["December"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Unscramble the following: yctpc nsuhilaiodea",
		"answers": ["Physical Education"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Unscramble the following: enno",
		"answers": ["Neon"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Unscramble the following: dvseli",
		"answers": ["Devils"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Unscramble the following: smruem",
		"answers": ["Summer"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Unscramble the following: etspla",
		"answers": ["Pastel"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Unscramble the following: beedta",
		"answers": ["Debate"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Unscramble the following: ebcle mmu",
		"answers": ["Meme Club"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Unscramble the following: optrgaphohy",
		"answers": ["Photography"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the name for the Greek goddess of victory?",
		"answers": ["Nike"]
	},
  {
		"question": "What city was buried by Mount Vesuvius in 79 A.D.?",
		"answers": ["Pompeii"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Where was the very first Hard Rock Cafe opened?",
		"answers": ["London"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Which President is on the United States 1,000 dollar bill?",
		"answers": ["Grover Cleveland"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Malcolm Little was a civil rights activist better known by what name?",
		"answers": ["Malcolm X"]
	},
	{
		"question": "In what year did the Titanic sink?",
		"answers": ["1912"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Who was the first US President to declare war?",
		"answers": ["James Madison"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What space shuttles name means to strive or make an earnest attempt?",
		"answers": ["Endeavour"]
	},
  {
		"question": "How many US presidents have been elected for two terms?",
		"answers": ["12"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What artist painted the late 15th century mural known as \"Last Supper\"?",
		"answers": ["Leonardo Da Vinci"]
	},
  {
		"question": "The second atomic bomb ever used in war-time was dropped on what city?",
		"answers": ["Nagasaki"]
	},
	{
		"question": "The sale of what was prohibited during prohibition?",
		"answers": ["Alcohol"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Which city is traditionally said to be built on seven hills?",
		"answers": ["Rome"]
	},
	{
		"question": "In which US state is US president JFK buried?",
		"answers": ["Virginia"]
	},
  {
		"question": "How many stripes are on the American flag?",
		"answers": ["13"]
	},
	{
		"question": "How many U.S. Presidents have there been?",
		"answers": ["45"]
	},
  {
		"question": "In what year did World War II end?",
		"answers": ["1945"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Where was the first drive in movie theater?",
		"answers": ["New Jersey"]
	},
  {
		"question": "In 1893, which country became the first to give women the right to vote?",
		"answers": ["New Zealand"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Which European country was the first to allow women to vote?",
		"answers": ["Finland"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Who painted the ceiling of the Sistine Chapel?",
		"answers": ["Michelangelo"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What month and year did the Sydney Harbour Bridge open?",
		"answers": ["March 1932"]
	},
  {
		"question": "In what year were the first Australian combat troops sent to Vietnam?",
		"answers": ["1965"]
	},
	{
		"question": "(Australia) The banning of which political party was ruled unconstitutional in March 1951?",
		"answers": ["The Communist Party"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Which Australian cities were shelled by Japanese submarines in June 1942?",
		"answers": ["Sydney and Newcastle"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What was the name of the volcano that erupted in pompeii?",
		"answers": ["Vesuvius"]
	},
  {
		"question": "What was the name of the power opposing the allies in WW2?",
		"answers": ["The axis"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the name of the body’s natural or acquired capability to resist certain diseases?",
		"answers": ["Immunity"]
	},
  {
		"question": "A snack made from marshmallows, graham crackers, chocolate and usually roasted over a campfire is called what?",
		"answers": ["S’mores"]
	},
	{
		"question": "How many colours does a rainbow have?",
		"answers": ["Seven colours"]
	},
  {
		"question": "The classic arcade game “pong” was manufactured by what company?",
		"answers": ["Atari"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Video game characters that cannot be controlled by players are called what?",
		"answers": ["NPCs"]
	},
  {
		"question": "How many players can simultaneously compete against each other in “fortnite battle royale”?",
		"answers": ["100"]
	},
	{
		"question": "The pickaxe is a basic tool used in what video game?",
		"answers": ["Minecraft"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Which president appears on the 1$ american bill",
		"answers": ["George washington"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Niagra falls is in which continent?",
		"answers": ["North america"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Charles darwin mainly worked in which branch of science?",
		"answers": ["Biology"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What was the name of the mission that landed the first man on the moon on the 20th of july 1969?",
		"answers": ["Apollo 11"]
	},
  {
		"question": "The mona lisa is displayed in which gallery?",
		"answers": ["The louvre"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Leonardo da vinci was from which country?",
		"answers": ["Italy"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Rainforest are characterised by what?",
		"answers": ["A high amount of rainfall"]
	},
	{
		"question": "How many days are there in a leap year?",
		"answers": ["366 days"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Karl marx was an influential figure in which  political movement?",
		"answers": ["Communism"]
	},
  {
		"question": "What is a positive integer that is equal to the sum of its proper positive divisors (excluding the number itself) called?",
		"answers": ["Perfect Number"]
	},
   {
		"question": "Is 8128 a perfect number?",
		"answers": ["Yes"]
	},
   {
		"question": "What is the 21st prime number?",
		"answers": ["ans 73", "73"]
	},
   {
		"question": "What is the sum of the angles of a triangle?",
		"answers": ["180 degrees", "180"]
	},
   {
		"question": "Continue this pattern: 144, 121, 100, 81, 64",
		"answers": ["49"]
	},
   {
		"question": "How many digits of pi are there?",
		"answers": ["infinity"]
	},
   {
		"question": "Name the number that is three more than one-fifth of one-tenth of one-half of 5,000.",
		"answers": ["ans 53", "53"]
	},
   {
		"question": "Two people are standing back to back. They each walk away from each other for three feet. Then they both turn left and walk for another four feet, and then stop. Now, how many feet apart are they standing?",
		"answers": ["ans 10", "10"]
	}
]